Finding aid to Amnesty International's Country Dossiers, Europe, Albania to Estonia.
IDC Publishers
- Belgium, 7
  - News releases, C
    - Belgium: Prompt action needed to address human rights concerns., 2 August 2004; (EUR 14/02/04); C10 (Microfiche 373)
    - Senegal: Government must immediately arrest and extradite Hissène Habré to Belgium to face crimes against humanity charges., 17 October 2005; (AFR 49/001/2005); C11 (Microfiche 397)
  - Newsletter entries, D
    - Belgium: European asylum policies., 12/1992; Amnesty International Newsletter December 1992 (Focus: In search of safety - Amnesty International's work with refugees).; D1 (Microfiche 133)
    - Belgium: Belgium's record on torture under scrutiny of UN., 1 July 2003; The Wire, July 2003. Vol. 33, No. 6.; (NWS 21/006/03); D2 (Microfiche 346)
  - General AI material / Background papers, E
    - The death penalty in Western Europe. (Extract), 15/6/1984; (EUR 01/01/84); E1 (Microfiche 48)
    - Belgium., 28/5/1986; The death penalty in Western Europe.; (EUR 03/02/86); E2 (Microfiche 65)
    - Belgium., 8/1987; The death penalty in Western Europe (Revised Edition August 1987).; (EUR 03/02/87); E3 (Microfiche 77)
    - Belgium: the death penalty., 5/1990; Amnesty International concerns in Western Europe, October 1989 - April 1990.; (EUR 03/01/90); E4 (Microfiche 110)
    - Belgium., 11/1990; Western Europe: Concerns May 1990 - October 1990.; (EUR 03/02/90); E5 (Microfiche 110)
    - Belgium: Progress towards abolition., 10/1991; Death Penalty News.; (ACT 53/04/91); E6 (Microfiche 119)
    - Belgium., 11/1991; Europe: Human rights and the need for a fair asylum policy.; (EUR 01/03/91); E7 (Microfiche 119)
    - Belgium: Progress of draft legislation abolishing the death penalty for peacetime offences., 11/1991; Concerns in Europe May - October 1991.; (EUR 01/02/91); E8 (Microfiche 119)
    - Belgium: ratifications., 11/1991; Concerns in Europe May - October 1991.; (EUR 01/02/91); E9 (Microfiche 119)
    - Belgium: Abolitionist in practice but not in law., 2/1992; Europe: Moving towards complete abolition of the death penalty.; (EUR 01/01/92); E10 (Microfiche 133)
    - Belgium: Ratifications., 1 February 1995; Concerns in Europe May-December 1994.; (EUR 01/01/95); E11 (Microfiche 184)
    - Belgium to abolish death penalty., 1 December 1995; Death penalty news December 1995.; (ACT 53/04/95); E12 (Microfiche 184)
    - Belgium., 1 March 1996; Concerns in Europe July - December 1995.; (EUR 01/01/96); E13 (Microfiche 204)
    - Belgium: Abolition bill (news in brief)., 1 June 1996; Death Penalty News June 1996.; (ACT 53/02/96); E14 (Microfiche 204)
    - Belgium: Progress on bills to abolish the death penalty., 1 July 1996; Abolition of the death penalty worldwide: developments in 1995.; (ACT 50/07/96); E15 (Microfiche 204)
    - Belgium., 1 August 1996; Concerns in Europe January - June 1996.; (EUR 01/02/96); E16 (Microfiche 204)
    - Belgium: Total abolition in Belgium., 1 October 1996; Death penalty news September 1996.; (ACT 53/03/96); E17 (Microfiche 204)
    - Belgium: Abolition of the death penalty., 1 June 1997; The death penalty worldwide: developments in 1996.; (ACT 50/05/97); E18 (Microfiche 223)
    - Belgium: Alleged human rights violations by members of the armed forces in Somalia., 1 September 1997; Concerns in Europe January - June 1997.; (EUR 01/06/97); E19 (Microfiche 223)
    - Belgium: Fining of Carriers by EU Member States., 1 October 1997; No Flights To Safety: Carrier Sanctions; Airline Employees and the Rights of Refugees.; (ACT 34/21/97); E20 (Microfiche 223)
    - Belgium: Alleged human rights violations committed in 1993 by soldiers participating in the UN multinational peace-keeping operation in Somalia., 1 February 1998; Concerns in Europe, July - December 1997.; (EUR 01/01/98); E21 (Microfiche 242)
    - Belgium: Alleged human rights violations by members of the armed forces in Somalia; report of the Council of Europe's Committee for the Prevention of Torture (CPT)., 1 September 1998; Concerns in Europe January-June 1998.; (EUR 01/02/98); E22 (Microfiche 242)
    - Belgium., 1 April 1999; Concerns in Europe July - December 1998.; (EUR 01/01/99); E23 (Microfiche 262)
    - Belgium: Correspondence with the government concerning the alleged ill-treatment of detained asylum-seekers., 1 June 1999; (EUR 14/01/99); E24 (Microfiche 262)
    - Belgium: Alleged ill-treatment of detained asylum-seekers., 1 August 1999; Concerns in Europe January - June 1999.; (EUR 01/02/99); E25 (Microfiche 262)
    - Belgium., 1 March 2000; Europe: Concerns in Europe July-December 1999.; (EUR 01/01/00); E26 (Microfiche 283)
    - Belgium., 21 August 2000; Europe: Concerns in Europe: January - June 2000.; (EUR 01/03/00); E27 (Microfiche 283)
    - Belgium: The death of Samira Adamu: Justice still awaited., 1 September 2000; (EUR 14/03/00); E28 (Microfiche 283)
    - Belgium: Death of Xhevdet Ferri., 1 October 2000; (EUR 14/04/00); E29 (Microfiche 283)
    - Belgium: the case of Semira Adamu., 6 November 2000; Failures at Fifty: Impunity for torture and ill-treatment in Europe on the 50th anniversary of the European Convention on Human Rights.; (EUR 01/04/00); E30 (Microfiche 283)
    - Belgium: The alleged ill-treatment of Charles Otu by Law Enforcement Officers., 1 December 2000; (EUR 14/06/00); E31 (Microfiche 283)
    - Belgium., 1 March 2001; Concerns in Europe July-December 2000.; (EUR 01/01/01); E32 (Microfiche 305)
    - Belgium., 1 September 2001; Concerns in Europe January - June 2001.; (EUR 01/03/01); E33 (Microfiche 305)
    - Universal Jurisdiction: Belgian court has jurisdiction in Sharon case to investigate 1982 Sabra and Chatila killings., 1 May 2002; (IOR 53/01/02); E34 (Microfiche 323)
    - Belgium., 30 May 2002; Concerns in Europe Bulletin: July - December 2001.; (EUR 01/02/02); E35 (Microfiche 323)
    - Belgium., 1 September 2002; Concerns in Europe January - June 2002.; (EUR 01/07/02); E36 (Microfiche 323)
    - Universal Jurisdiction: Belgian prosecutors can investigate crimes under international law committed abroad., 1 February 2003; (IOR 53/001/03); E37 (Microfiche 347)
    - Iraq: Europe and the crisis in Iraq: Statement to the Parliamentary Assembly of the Council of Europe., 2 April 2003; (MDE 14/052/03); E38 (Microfiche 347)
    - Belgium: Before the UN Committee against torture: alleged police ill-treatment., 28 May 2003; (EUR 14/001/03); E39 (Microfiche 347)
    - Belgium: Alleged ill-treatment and verbal, including racist, abuse of Bernardin Mbuku and Odette Ibanda by Brussels police officers., 1 July 2003; (EUR 14/002/03); E40 (Microfiche 347)
    - Belgium., 1 October 2003; Concerns in Europe and Central Asia January - June 2003.; (EUR 01/016/03); E41 (Microfiche 348)
    - Belgium: Stop Violence Against Women. Breaking the cycle of violence., 5 March 2004; (EUR 14/01/04); E42 (Microfiche 373)
    - Belgium: Europe and Central Asia: Concerns in Europe and Central Asia: July - December 2003., 1 May 2004; (EUR 01/01/04); E43 (Microfiche 373)
    - Belgium:, 1 September 2004; Europe and Central Asia: Summary of Amnesty International's Concerns in the Region January - June 2004.; (EUR 01/05/04); E44 (Microfiche 373)
    - Belgium., 1 September 2005; Europe and Central Asia: Summary of Amnesty International's Concerns in the Region: July - December 2004.; (EUR 01/002/2005); E45 (Microfiche 397)
    - Belgium., 1 December 2005; Europe Central Asia: Summary of Amnesty International's Concerns in the Region: January - June 2005.; (EUR 01/012/2005); E46 (Microfiche 397)
- Bosnia-Herzegovina, 8
  - Publications, A
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina., 20 October 1993; Conspiracy of terror: political killings and disappearances'' in the 1990s - Amnesty International briefing.; (ACT 33/35/93) (includes photograph); A1 (Microfiche 149)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina., 20 October 1993; Getting away with murder: political killings and disappearances'' in the 1990s.; (ACT 33/25/93) (photograph); A2 (Microfiche 149)
  - Annual Report entry, B
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina., 1 July 1993; Amnesty International Report 1993.; (POL 10/01/93); B1 (Microfiche 149)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina., 8 July 1993; Annual Report updates.; (POL 10/04/93); B2 (Microfiche 149)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina., 7 July 1994; Amnesty International Report 1994.; (POL 10/02/94); B3 (Microfiche 166)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina., 1 July 1995; Amnesty International Report 1995.; (POL 10/01/95); B4 (Microfiche 184)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina., 6 July 1995; Amnesty International Report 1995 updates.; (POL 10/04/95); B5 (Microfiche 184)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina., 18 June 1996; Amnesty International Report 1996.; (POL 10/02/96); B6 (Microfiche 204)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina., 18 June 1997; Amnesty International Report 1997.; (POL 10/01/97); B7 (Microfiche 224)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina., 17 June 1998; Amnesty International Report 1998.; (POL 10/01/98); B8 (Microfiche 242)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina., 16 June 1999; Amnesty International Report 1999.; (POL 10/01/99); B9 (Microfiche 262)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina., 14 June 2000; Amnesty International Report 2000.; (POL 10/01/00); B10 (Microfiche 283)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina., 30 May 2001; Amnesty International Report 2001.; (POL 10/01/01); B11 (Microfiche 305)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina., 28 May 2002; Amnesty International Report 2002.; (POL 10/01/02); B12 (Microfiche 323)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina., 28 May 2003; Amnesty International Report 2003.; (POL 10/003/03); B13 (Microfiche 348)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina., 26 May 2004; Amnesty International Report 2004.; (POL 10/04/04); B14 (Microfiche 373)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina., 25 May 2005; Amnesty International Report 2005.; (POL 10/001/2005); B15 (Microfiche 397)
  - News releases, C
    - Amnesty International News Release: Human rights violations in Bosnia-Herzegovina and Kosovo., 23/10/1992; (EUR 63/02/92); C1 (Microfiche 133)
    - Amnesty International News Release: Bosnia-Herzegovina: Rape and other human rights violations still going on., 21 January 1993; (EUR 63/02/93); C1 (Microfiche 149)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Amnesty International delegate visits Croatia., 28 March 1994; Amnesty International News Service 60/94.; (NWS 11/60/94); C2 (Microfiche 166)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Bosnian Serb forces responsible for new abuses against minorities., 5 April 1994; AI News Service 65/94.; (NWS 11/65/94); C3 (Microfiche 166)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Aid workers held in Bosnia may be hostages., 5 May 1994; AI News Service 94/94.; (NWS 11/94/94); C4 (Microfiche 166)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Amnesty International concerned at disappearance'' of Tunisian aid workers in Bosnia-Herzegovina., 9 June 1994; Amnesty International News Service 121/94.; (NWS 11/121/94); C5 (Microfiche 166)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Amnesty International calls on Bosnian Serb authorities to protect detainees., 17 July 1995; (EUR 63/14/95); C6 (Microfiche 184)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Amnesty International is concerned about the safety of non-Serbs in Bosnian Serb-controlled areas., 9 August 1995; (EUR 63/18/95); C7 (Microfiche 184)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Human rights abuses committed by Bosnian-Serb forces against Muslims during the capture of Srebrenica., 11 August 1995; (EUR 63/19/95); C8 (Microfiche 184)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Statement at ICM press conference, 11 August 1995, Lubljana, Slovenia., (EUR 63/20/95); C9 (Microfiche 184)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Amnesty International calls on parties to ensure human rights guarantees., 17 November 1995; (EUR 63/29/95); C10 (Microfiche 184)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Impunity and right to return - danger areas of peace agreement., 22 November 1995; (EUR 63/30/95); C11 (Microfiche 184)
    - Bosnia-Herzogovina: Amnesty International calls on governments not to rush the return of refugees., 15 January 1996; (EUR 63/03/96); C12 (Microfiche 204)
    - Bosnia-Herzogovina: Amnesty International urges IFOR to search for war criminals and not to allow the destruction of evidence., 22 January 1996; (EUR 63/04/96); C13 (Microfiche 204)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Amnesty International delegation finds country not safe for refugees to return and implementation of Dayton agreement human rights provisions faltering., 12 June 1996; (EUR 63/16/96); C14 (Microfiche 204)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: One year after the Srebrenica tragedy, Amnesty demands truth and justice for Srebrenica victims and the other missing'' and disappeared''., 3 July 1996; (EUR 63/22/96); C15 (Microfiche 204)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Opinion piece on the London conference., 27 November 1996; (EUR 63/31/96); C16 (Microfiche 204)
    - Bosnia Herzegovina: First hearing of human rights chamber considers case of missing'' Matanovics., 6 February 1997; (EUR 63/02/97); C17 (Microfiche 224)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Amnesty International condemns unfair trial of Zvornik Seven''., 24 April 1997; (EUR 63/07/97); C18 (Microfiche 224)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: From promise to reality: Agenda for the international community and the new High Representative., 12 June 1997; (EUR 63/11/97); C19 (Microfiche 224)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Media advisory: launch of action: Arrest Now!, 8 July 1997; (EUR 63/16/97); C20 (Microfiche 224)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Media advisory: launch of action: Arrest Now!, 9 July 1997; (EUR 63/17/97); C21 (Microfiche 224)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: There is less than a year left: Arrest Now!, 11 July 1997; (EUR 63/15/97); C22 (Microfiche 224)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: There are still at least 66 indictees at large -Arrest Now!, 11 July 1997; (EUR 63/18/97); C23 (Microfiche 224)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Joint statement by Amnesty International, Human Rights Watch, Institute for War and Peace Reporting., 11 July 1997; (EUR 63/19/97); C24 (Microfiche 224)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Surrender of suspects is no reason for international complacency., 9 October 1997; (EUR 63/23/97); C25 (Microfiche 224)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: End lip-service to justice -- Arrest Now!, 11 December 1997; (EUR 63/27/97); C26 (Microfiche 224)
    - Refugees from Former Yugoslavia - Send the right message for Kosovo: learn from and remedy the policy failures over Bosnia and Croatia''., 25 June 1998; (EUR 05/01/98); C27 (Microfiche 242)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Judgment on Celebici trial a step towards justice., 16 November 1998; (EUR 63/12/98); C28 (Microfiche 242)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Retrial of Zvornik Seven'' repeats serious violations of fair trial standards., 15 December 1998; (EUR 63/14/98); C29 (Microfiche 242)
    - Former Yugoslavia: AI appeals to Government representatives to finally resolve the issue of missing persons., 24 March 1999; (EUR 05/01/99); C30 (Microfiche 262)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Arrest by SFOR troops - a positive step., 8 June 1999; (EUR 63/03/99); C31 (Microfiche 262)
    - Bosnia Herzegovina: The forgotten of Srebrenica - another snub to justice., 9 July 1999; (EUR 63/04/99); C32 (Microfiche 262)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Bosnian Serb authorities must act to stop violent attacks on media., 5 November 1999; (EUR 63/06/99); C33 (Microfiche 262)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Ahmici verdict - Justice needs to go further., 14 January 2000; (EUR 63/01/00); C34 (Microfiche 283)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Blaskic trial, a milestone in the achievement of justice for war crimes., 3 March 2000; (EUR 63/03/00); C35 (Microfiche 283)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Bosnian-Serbs' decision to cooperate with tribunal - a major step forward., 5 April 2000; (EUR 63/04/00); C36 (Microfiche 284)
    - World Press Freedom Day - Journalists risk life and limb to report the news., 3 May 2000; (ACT 78/01/00); C37 (Microfiche 284)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Srebrenica must not become another statistic of war., 11 July 2000; (EUR 63/10/00); C38 (Microfiche 284)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Supreme Court should hear Garaplija., 4 October 2000; (EUR 63/11/00); C39 (Microfiche 284)
    - Bosnia/Herzegovina: Peace without justice., 17 November 2000; (EUR 63/14/00); C40 (Microfiche 284)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Foca verdict - rape and sexual enslavement are crimes against humanity., 22 February 2001; (EUR 63/04/01); C41 (Microfiche 305)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Accountability at the Hague still needed at the highest level., 26 February 2001; (EUR 63/05/01); C42 (Microfiche 305)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Political violence a severe setback for minority returns., 10 May 2001; (EUR 63/07/01); C43 (Microfiche 305)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Freedom of worship at risk amidst climate of impunity., 18 June 2001; (EUR 63/08/01); C44 (Microfiche 305)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Srebrenica - how much longer before Karadzic and Mladic will face the Tribunal?, 9 July 2001; (EUR 63/09/01); C45 (Microfiche 305)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: General Radislav Krstic found guilty of genocide., 2 August 2001; (EUR 63/10/01); C46 (Microfiche 305)
    - Europe: Thousands of disappeared'' await justice., 30 August 2001; (EUR 01/04/01); C47 (Microfiche 305)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Violence against minorities in Republika Srpska must stop., 10 November 2001; (EUR 63/13/01); C48 (Microfiche 305)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Some dignity at last for victims of disappearance'' in Prijedor., 23 November 2001; (EUR 63/14/01); C49 (Microfiche 305)
    - Bosnia- Herzegovina: Transfer of six Algerians to US custody puts them at risk., 17 January 2002; (EUR 63/01/02); C50 (Microfiche 323)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Letter to the US Ambassador regarding six Algerian men., 18 January 2002; (EUR 63/03/02); C51 (Microfiche 323)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: No justice for victims of war crimes as long as perpetrators remain at large., 6 April 2002; (EUR 63/08/02); C52 (Microfiche 323)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Redress for Srebrenica., 11 July 2002; (EUR 63/11/02); C53 (Microfiche 323)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Amnesty International calls for new commitments on the International Day of the Disappeared''., 30 August 2002; (EUR 63/16/02); C54 (Microfiche 323)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Human rights chambers decision in the Algerians case must be implemented by Bosnia., 11 October 2002; (EUR 63/17/02); C55 (Microfiche 323)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: SFOR detention violates human rights., 27 November 2002; (EUR 63/19/02); C56 (Microfiche 323)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Recommendations on the European Union Police Mission., 13 January 2003; (EUR 63/001/03); C57 (Microfiche 348)
    - EU-Bosnia: Disappearances'' Must Be Addressed., 5 March 2003; (EUR 01/003/03); C58 (Microfiche 348)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Time to end impunity for 'disappearances'., 5 March 2003; (EUR 63/006/03); C59 (Microfiche 348)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Human Rights Chamber decision on Srebrenica - a first step to justice., 7 March 2003; (EUR 63/007/03); C60 (Microfiche 348)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: dignified burials for the victims of Srebrenica a vital condition for just peace and reconciliation., 31 March 2003; (EUR 63/008/03); C61 (Microfiche 348)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: The government should reject US impunity agreement., 16 May 2003; (EUR 63/011/03); C62 (Microfiche 348)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Abolition of Human Rights Chamber leaves citizens unprotected., 11 June 2003; (EUR 63/015/03); C63 (Microfiche 348)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: The Disappeared'' must not be forgotten., 30 August 2003; (EUR 63/017/03); C64 (Microfiche 348)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Justice cannot be achieved on the cheap., 12 November 2003; (EUR 63/021/03); C65 (Microfiche 348)
    - EU Foreign Ministers today: New EU force in Bosnia-Herzegovina must not make the same mistakes as SFOR''., 12 July 2004; (EUR 01/04/04); C66 (Microfiche 373)
    - Bosnia and Herzegovina: Ten years on and no justice for the victims of Srebrenica., 8 July 2005; (EUR 63/007/2005); C67 (Microfiche 397)
    - Bosnia and Herzegovina: From Dayton and beyond., 14 December 2005; (EUR 63/010/2005); C68 (Microfiche 397)
  - Newsletter entries, D
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: photograph of an extrajudicial execution., 8/1992; Amnesty International Newsletter August 1992 (Focus - Getting away with murder).; D1 (Microfiche 133)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Suffering continues as civil war escalates., 11/1992; Amnesty International Newsletter November 1992 (includes photograph).; D2 (Microfiche 133)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Sandzak Muslims abducted from Serbian-held areas., 1 May 1993; Amnesty International Newsletter May 1993.; (NWS 21/02/93); D3 (Microfiche 149)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Civilian casualties mount as war rages on., 1 August 1993; Amnesty International Newsletter August 1993.; (NWS 21/05/93) (includes photograph); D4 (Microfiche 149)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Licence to kill - political killings and disappearances'' focus., 1 October 1993; Amnesty International Newsletter October 1993.; (NWS 21/07/93) (photograph); D5 (Microfiche 149)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Women in the war zone., 1 March 1994; AI Newsletter March 1994 (Focus - Women under attack).; (NWS 21/03/94); D6 (Microfiche 166)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: People forced to flee homes after Bosnian Serb brutality., 1 June 1994; AI Newsletter June 1994.; (NWS 21/06/94); D7 (Microfiche 166)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina., 1 March 1995; Amnesty International Newsletter March 1995 (Focus - Human rights are a woman's right).; (NWS 21/03/95); D8 (Microfiche 184)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Disappeared'' must not be forgotten., 1 October 1995; Amnesty International Newsletter October 1995.; (NWS 21/10/95); D9 (Microfiche 184)
    - Bosnia and Herzogovina: Abduction of Nura Berbic, Hasnija Demirovic (Worldwide appeals)., 1 February 1996; (NWS 21/02/96); D10 (Microfiche 204)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Police fail to protect returnees, Hazim Sahman., 1 September 1997; Worldwide appeals October 1997.; (NWS 22/05/97); D11 (Microfiche 224)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Human rights workshops for Sarajevo's youth., 1 November 1997; Amnesty International Newsletter November 1997.; (NWS 21/6/97); D12 (Microfiche 224)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Violence against returnees., 18 June 1998; Amnesty Works: Updates to AI appeals and features about AI's impact. May 1998.; (NWS 22/04/98); D13 (Microfiche 242)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Nura Berbic, Hasnija Demirovic., 18 June 1998; Amnesty Works: Updates to AI appeals and features about AI's impact. May 1998.; (NWS 22/04/98); D14 (Microfiche 242)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Bosniac returnees., 18 June 1998; Amnesty Works: Updates to AI appeals and features about AI's impact. May 1998.; (NWS 22/04/98); D15 (Microfiche 242)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Nura Berbic and Hasnija Demirovic., 1 March 1999; AI Works: Updates to Worldwide Appeals and news about the impact of Amnesty International. March 1999.; (NWS 22/01/99); D16 (Microfiche 262)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Bosnia returnees., 1 March 1999; AI Works: Updates to Worldwide Appeals and news about the impact of Amnesty International. March 1999.; (NWS 22/01/99); D17 (Microfiche 262)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: A decade without answers for victims of Srebrenica massacre., 1 July 2005; The Wire, July 2005. Vol. 35, No.6.; (NWS 21/006/2005); D18 (Microfiche 397)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Worldwide appeals: Bosnia and Herzegovina: 'Disappeared' for 10 years., 1 August 2005; The Wire, August 2005. Vol. 35, No.7.; (NWS 21/007/2005); D19 (Microfiche 397)
  - General AI material / Background papers, E
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: New reports of human rights violations and village massacre., 17/6/1992; Weekly Update Service 24/92.; (NWS 11/24/92); E1 (Microfiche 133)
    - Former Yugoslavia: Amnesty International concerned about reports of human rights violations in Bosnia-Herzegovina., 7/8/1992; Weekly Update Service 31/92.; (NWS 11/31/92 add); E2 (Microfiche 133)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina: Investigation team finds extensive human rights abuses., 7/9/1992; Weekly Update Service 35/92.; (NWS 11/35/92 add); E3 (Microfiche 133)